Praveen George Ryan

Web developer



p.g.ryan333@gmail.com

https://p-g-ryan-portfolio.vercel.app

• 5-27-399/1, Subhash Chandra Bose Nagar, Hyderabad -500055



About Me

I am a passionate web developer with a passion for web development. I specialize in building websites and web applications using modern technologies like Next.js, JavaScript, React and MongoDB. I leverage the MERN Stack to create beautiful, user-friendly websites and applications that deliver real results. With a perfect completion rate on all projects I've undertaken and 15+ satisfied clients, I'm dedicated to turning your ideas into reality. I bring a positive, enthusiastic attitude and a love for web development, ensuring a smooth and successful collaboration.



English Fluent
Hindi Conversational
Telugu Native



★ Skills

NextJS

JavaScript

React

Python

HTML

CSS

MongoDB



Certificates

Complete NextJS Full Stack Developer



Education

KGR institute of Technology and Management

M.pharmacy

Gland Institute of Pharmaceutical Sciences

B.Pharmacy



Experiences

Granules India Limited

2021 - 2023

2019 - 2022

2015 - 2019

Quality Assurance Executive

As a Formulator in the pharmaceutical industry, I leveraged data analysis tools to optimize pre-formulation, ensuring safe, high-quality medications reach patients faster. I meticulously analyzed drug properties, conducted compatibility studies, and oversaw technology transfer.

Freelancer

2023 - Till Now

Web Developer

Full-stack web developer with 1.5 years of experience in building robust and scalable web applications. Proficient in both frontend and backend development using modern technologies such as Next.js, React, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, and MongoDB.